<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>https://syntacticnacl.com/</link><description>Recent content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>2024</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://syntacticnacl.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Needs More Salt… Why You Should Care About Libsodium</title><link>https://syntacticnacl.com/talks/libsodium/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://syntacticnacl.com/talks/libsodium/</guid><description>Cryptography has never been an approachable subject, especially when it comes to computing. Libsodium has set out to change that. We hear about systems being compromised on a daily basis with millions of passwords out on the web free to use to access other site’s accounts and systems. This is unacceptable! What happens when these systems are compromised? Can crackers access your “encrypted” data? Can they access your “hashed” passwords? In this April 4th, 2019 presentation, I discuss proper hashing mechanisms for passwords, libsodium, and encryption and how it relates to our PHP applications and systems.</description></item><item><title>Scotchbox</title><link>https://syntacticnacl.com/talks/scotchbox/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://syntacticnacl.com/talks/scotchbox/</guid><description>In this July 7th, 2016 minitalk presentation, I talk about provisioning a Scotch Box VM virtual machine.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://syntacticnacl.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://syntacticnacl.com/about/</guid><description>Hi, my name is Garrett. I am passionate about the topics of cryptography, privacy, and blockchain technologies and their practical applications in today’s technology infused world. In my free time, I enjoy playing various table-top games, reading, playing guitar and mandolin, hiking, perusing whitepapers, and playing with obscure *nix operating systems.
Also in my free time, I do my best to give back to the community. I am currently a DEF CON Demo Labs Goon, Blue Team Village volunteer, open source contributor, and have published a CVE in a popular 2FA library.</description></item></channel></rss>